Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  - Seeing Washington in one, two, three days., Circa [193-?]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 190
  - Washington, the city for all Americans., Circa [1955]; Series 2; 52 pages: illustrations, map; 17 cm (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 191
  - Sightseeing Washington and vicinity: Town House Tours by Limousine., Circa [195-?]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (6 pages): illustrations; 23 x 30 cm folded to 23 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 192
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) Tours.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Tours. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423866
  - So -- you want to see Washington: 10 three-hour tours of the nation's capital., Circa [194-?]; Series 2; 7 pages: illustrations, map; 28 x 22 cm folded to 14 x 11 cm (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 193
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) Tours.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871; Tours. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423866
  - So -- you want to see Washington: 2 two-hour tours of the nation's capital., Circa [194-?]; Series 2; 1 sheet (8 pages): map; 27 x 21 cm folded to 14 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 194
  - SAS city portrait: Washington., Circa [196-?]; Series 2; 23 pages: color illustrations, map; 24 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 195
  - Highlights of the national capital and its historic environs prepared by the Greater National Capital Committee of the Washington Board of Trade., Circa [193-?]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (16 pages): illustrations; 23 cm (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 196
    Subjects: Washington Metropolitan Area Guidebooks.; Washington (D.C.) Metropolitan Area. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243122; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - The Diamond chatterbox. Oct. 13, 1940., Circa [1940]; Series 2; 12 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 197
  - Greater Washington Council of Organizations Serving International Visitors, International Visitors Information Service -- invites you -- come to Washington [author, Katherine Walker; prepared by the Greater Washington Council of Organizations Serving International Visitors]., Circa [1964]; Series 2; 16 pages: illustrations, map; 18 x 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 198
    Cataloger notes: "June 1964."; Cover title.
    Subjects: Visitors, Foreign Washington (D.C.); Visitors, Foreign. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01167960; Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Your guide to Washington, D.C. [by K.M. Birkhead, K.R. Harding]., Circa [1954]; Series 2; 1 sheet (12 pages): illustrations, map; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 199
    Cataloger notes: Presented by Alan Bible, U.S. Senator from Nevada.
  - Sightseeing in Washington, D.C. and vicinity: schedules of daily sightseeing tours., 1965; Series 2; 1 folded sheet ([16] pages): illustrations (some color); 23 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 201
    Cataloger notes: Tour brochure for Washington, D.C. area.
    Subjects: Tourism Washington Metropolitan Area.; Tourism. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01153142; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington Metropolitan Area Description and travel.; Washington (D.C.) Metropolitan Area. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243122
  - Diamond Sightseeing Tours welcomes you to Washington, D.C., the nation's capital., Circa [196-?]; Series 2; 1 sheet ([12] pages): color illustrations, color map; 23 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 202
  - Vistors guide: handy pocket guide to the naton's capital., Circa [1965]; ??1965; Series 2; 28 unnumbered pages: illustrations, maps; 22 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 203
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Distributed to the 1965 Leadership Conference, Chamber of Commerce of the U.S., 53rd annual meeting, April 25-28, 1965.
  - Sen. Charles E. Potter welcomes you to your nation's capital., Circa [195-?]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (16 pages): illustrations, map, portrait; 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 204
  - Traveler's guide to Northern Virginia and the Nation's Capital ..., Circa [19--?]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (8 pages): illustrations, map; 23 cm (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 205
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Virginia Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85143759; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Virginia. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204597; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Washington vita by Willis Thornton., 1947; Series 2; pages 33-39; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 206
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Imprimatur: a literary quarterly for bibliophiles. Vol. 1, numbers 2-3 (April-July, 1947).
    Subjects: Glass, Francis, 1790-1824. Life of George Washington, in Latin prose. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50033093; Washington, George, 1732-1799. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n81080571
  - Washington in 1859., Series 2; pages [1]-17: illustrations; 26 cm (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 210
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Harper's new monthly magazine. Vol. 20, numbers 115 (Dec. 1859).; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 198
  - List of principal municipal authorities of the cities of Washington, Georgetown and the District of Columbia compiled by John B. Larner., Circa [1920]; Series 2; pages 180-187; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 211
    Cataloger notes: "Reprinted from The Records of the Columbia Historical Society, Vol. 23, 1920."; Cover title.; In gray paper covers printed in black.
    Subjects: Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; Washington (D.C.) Politics and government. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145356; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Washington the winter before the war by Henry L. Dawes., Circa [1893]; Series 2; pages 160-167 pages; 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 213
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Atlantic monthly. Aug., 1893.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 198
    Subjects: American Civil War (1861-1865) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01351658; 1861 - 1865 fast; Washington (D.C.) History Civil War, 1861-1865. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145354; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - New York Seventh Regiment: our march to Washington by [T. Trowbridge]., Circa [1861]; Series 2; pages 744-756; 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 214
    Cataloger notes: Author from: Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 142.; Caption title.; Detached from: Atlantic monthly. June, 1861.
    Subjects: United States. Army. Regiment Infantry, New York Volunteers, 7th (1861-1863); Washington (D.C.) History Civil War, 1861-1865. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145354
  - Battle of Bladensburg (from the Society's collections)., Circa [1910]; Series 2; pages 341-349; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 215
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Maryland historical magazine. Vol. 5, numbers 4 (Dec. 1910).
    Subjects: Bladensburg, Battle of (Maryland: 1814) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01404420; 1814 fast; Bladensburg, Battle of, Bladensburg, Md., 1814. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85014742; Maryland Bladensburg. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01237977
  - Centennial of the nation's capital by F.W. Fitzpatrick., Circa [1900]; Series 2; pages [109]-120: illustrations, portrait; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 216
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: The Cosmpolitan. Vol. 30, numbers 2 (Dec. 1900).; In blue-gray paper covers.
  - The Smithsonian Institution., Circa [1871]; Series 2; pages 401-402; 28 cm (Box 5, Folder 37)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 217
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Nature. Vol. 4 (Sept. 21, 1871).
  - Letters relating to the capture of Washington by John C. Hildt., Circa [1907]; Series 2; pages 58-66; 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 38)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 218
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: The South Atlantic Quarterly. Jan. 1907.
    Subjects: Capture of Washington by the British (1814) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01352241; War of 1812. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01199067; 1812 - 1815 fast; United States History War of 1812. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140194; Washington (D.C.) History Capture by the British, 1814. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145353; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - The Smithsonian Institution and the National Museum by Ausburn Towner., Circa [1890]; Series 2; pages 148-159: illustrations; 29 cm (Box 5, Folder 39)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 219
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Frank Leslie's popular monthly. Feb. 1890.; In navy blue paper covers.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 173
  - Our capital by [Wm. R. Hooper]., Circa [1870]; Series 2; pages 42-52; 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 40)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 220
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Lippincott's magazine. Jan. 1870.; Signed Wm. R. Hooper on pages 52.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 29
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Washington on the eve of the War., Undated; Series 2; pages 458-466; 24 cm. (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 221
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Signed: Charles P. Stone.
  - Men and affairs at Washington by David S. Barry., Circa [1907]; Series 2; pages 209-224: illustrations, portraits; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 42)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 222
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: New England magazine. Oct. 1907.
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) Politics and government. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145356; Washington (D.C.) Religious life and customs.
  - The Ontonagon copper bowlder in the U.S. National Museum. By Charles Moore., Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 223
    Cataloger notes: Half-title.; Also issued online.
    Subjects: Boulders. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85016086; Copper. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85032278; Boulders. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00837070; Copper. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00878331
  - The Army Medical Museum at Washington., Circa 1871; Series 2; pages 233-242; 27 cm (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 224
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Printed in two columns.; Reprinted from Lippincott's magazine of popular literature and science, volume 7, Mar. 1871.; Signed at end: J.J. Woodward.; Includes bibliographical references.; Condition reviewed 20150602 conservation not necessary pda DNLM; Will digitize 20140224 pda DNLM
    Subjects: Army Medical Museum (U.S.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n82031690; Army Medical Museum (U.S.); Army Medical Museum (U.S.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00565951; Military Medicine United States.; Museums United States.
  - The Smithsonian Institution by Henry Carrington Bolton., Circa [1896]; Series 2; pages [289]-303, 449-464: illustrations, portrait; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 225
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Appleton's popular science monthly. Jan., Feb. 1896.; Part I. Origin of the Institution -- Part II. Activities of the Institution.
  - Up the Potomac., Circa [1862]; Series 2; pages 27-29; 28 cm (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 226
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: The Leisure hour. 1862.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, 151
    Subjects: Napier, Charles, 1786-1860. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n90653046; Napier, Charles, 1786-1860 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01774648; Capture of Washington by the British (1814) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01352241; 1814 fast; Washington (D.C.) History Capture by the British, 1814. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145353; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - The robbery of St. Inigo's house., Circa [1873]; Series 2; pages [553-557?]: illustrations; 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 227
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: American historical record. Dec. 1873.
    Subjects: Capture of Washington by the British (1814) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01352241; 1814 fast; Washington (D.C.) History Capture by the British, 1814. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145353; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Burning of Washington, 1814 [unpublished letter] contributed by James W. Gerard., Circa [1892]; Series 2; pages 467-468; 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 228
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: The Magazine of American history. June, 1892.
  - A sketch of Washington City by Anne C. Lynch., Circa [1852]; Series 2; 15 pages: illustrations, map; 26 cm (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 229
    Cataloger notes: Detached from: Harper's new monthly magazine. Vol. 6, numbers 31 (Dec. 1852).
    Subjects: Public buildings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145360; Public buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01082090; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Matthew B. Brady, 1823-1896 by Charles Flato., Circa [approximately 1930]; Series 2; pages [35]-41, [6] leaves of plates: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 230
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from an issue of The Hound and Horn.
    Subjects: Brady, Mathew B., approximately 1823-1896. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n81140569; Brady, Mathew B., approximately 1823-1896 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01809348; Photographers United States Biography. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008109265; Photographers. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01061605; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Biography. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423686
  - Early days at the national capital by D.E. Roberts., Circa [approximately 1900]; Series 2; pages [371]-377: illustrations; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 231
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from an unidentified periodical.
    Subjects: United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85141041; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - National Institute., Circa [1845]; Series 2; 235-255 pages 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 52)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 232
    Cataloger notes: From the American review: a Whig journal ... volume 2, 1845.
    Subjects: National Institute for the Promotion of Science. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n86845669; National Institute for the Promotion of Science. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00614268
  - The Mentor. Vol. 1, numbers 3 (March 3, 1913)., Circa [1913]; Series 2; 12 pages, [6] leaves of plates: illustrations; 26 cm (Box 5, Folder 53)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 233
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Entire issue is: Washington the capital / by Dwight L. Elmendorf.; Includes bibliographical references (page 11).
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, the by S.G.W. Benjamin., Circa [1882]; Series 2; pages [815]-825: illustrations; 26 cm (Box 5, Folder 54)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 234
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: The Century magazine. Oct. 1882.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 49
    Subjects: Corcoran Gallery of Art. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79079587; Corcoran Gallery of Art. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00534875
  - Facts about Washington compiled by the Washington Board of Trade., Circa [192-?]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 25 cm (Box 5, Folder 55)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 235
  - Catalogue sale of valuable law library of the late E.C. Morgan (by order of the Orphans' Court, District of Columbia): to which is added a valuable medical library ... to be sold at our auction rooms ... on Thursday evening, Sept. 5th, 1867 J.T. Coldwell and Company., Circa [1867?]; Series 2; 12 pages; 23 cm (Box 5, Folder 56)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 236
    Subjects: Morgan, E. C. Library.
  - Seeing the nation's capital, Washington, D.C., Circa [194-?]; Series 2; 1 sheet: illustrations; 26 x 36 cm (Box 5, Folder 57)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 237
    Cataloger notes: Illustrated place mat.
  - An announcement from the National Park Service to out-of-town groups visiting Washington, D.C., 1962; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (16 pages): illustrations; 24 cm (Box 5, Folder 58)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 238
  - In memoriam [Samuel Hensel Giesy, D.D.]., 1888; Series 2; pages 149-161; 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 59)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 239
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Half title: Parish Guide, July 1988, volume 12, numbers 7.
    Subjects: Giesy. John Ulric, 1826-1888.
  - Welcome to Washington 1976., Circa [1976]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet: illustrations, map; 47 x 30 cm, folded to 24 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 60)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 240
    Cataloger notes: "*GPO: 1976--211-308/114. Revised 1976."; Title from cover.
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) Maps. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117384; Washington (D.C.) Tours.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505; Maps. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01423704; Tourist maps fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01423809; Tourist maps. lcgft http://id.loc.gov/authorities/genreForms/gf2011026699; Tours. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01423866
  - The Smithsonian Institution by Henry W. Elliott., Circa [1879]; Series 2; pages [688]-700; 25 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 241
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: International review (New York, N.Y.: 1874). Dec. 1879.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 172
  - The Smithsoniana Institution by [W.H.H.]., Circa [1854]; Series 2; pages 385-395; 24 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 242
    Cataloger notes: Author from: Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 172.; Cover title.; Detached from: The Christian examiner and religious miscellany. Nov. 1854.
  - The fourth of March., Circa [1865]; Series 2; pages 274-286; 24 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 243
    Cataloger notes: Author from: Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 109.; Cover title.; Detached from: Christian Examiner (Boston, Mass.). March 1865.
    Subjects: Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865 Inauguration, 1865.; Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00030184; 1861 - 1865 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; United States Politics and government 1861-1865. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140441; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Society in Washington by H.J.R., Circa [1872]; Series 2; pages 99-102; 24 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 244
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: American homes. Vol. 1, numbers 3 (Jan. 1872).
  - Miss Martineau's Society in America, and Grund's American society., Circa [1837?]; Series 2; pages 404-424; 25 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 245
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Tait's Edinburgh magazine. July 1837.
    Subjects: Grund, Francis J. (Francis Joseph), 1804-1863. Americans in their moral, social, and political relations. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n88101272; Martineau, Harriet, 1802-1876. Society in America. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79027175; United States Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140006; United States Politics and government 1829-1837. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140430; United States Social life and customs. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140527; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349
  - The jurist, and law miscellany. Vol. 1, numbers 5 (August 4, 1834)., Circa 1834; Series 2; pages 169-224, 25-32; 25 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 246
    Cataloger notes: "Containing condensed reports of cases argued and decided in the Supreme Court of the United States."; Cover title.; Edited by William Cranch.
    Subjects: United States. Supreme Court.; United States. Supreme Court. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00529481; Law United States. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85075193; Law. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00993678; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - 24 hikes in and near Washington., Circa [1947]; Series 2; 32 pages: maps; 21 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 248
    Subjects: Hiking Washington Metropolitan Area.; Hiking. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00956758; Washington (D.C.) Metropolitan Area. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243122
  - Circuit hikes in the Shenandoah National Park by Potomac Appalachian Trail Club., Circa [1955]; Series 2; 40 pages: maps; 22 cm. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 249
    Cataloger notes: "May 1955."
    Subjects: Hiking Virginia Shenandoah National Park Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009126334; Hiking. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00956758; Shenandoah National Park (Va.) Guidebooks.; Virginia Shenandoah National Park. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01278630; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Recreational opportunities available to Washington., Circa [1934]; Series 2; [2], 57 pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 251